[
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x6f6f5265717565737465723a63313836666139313433353363343462326533336562653035663231383436663130343862656461",
        "timestamp": 1769296835,
        "question": "Across V2",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x6f6f5265717565737465723a63313836666139313433353363343462326533336562653035663231383436663130343862656461",
        "timestamp": 1769292323,
        "question": "Across V2",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x6f6f5265717565737465723a63313836666139313433353363343462326533336562653035663231383436663130343862656461",
        "timestamp": 1769286623,
        "question": "Across V2",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x6f6f5265717565737465723a63313836666139313433353363343462326533336562653035663231383436663130343862656461",
        "timestamp": 1769280623,
        "question": "Across V2",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a313061366165643833363061666235663936346338646462653366373433353962333936333466313065333039366266613734626462656334313366346536382c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323037343136392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769267988,
        "question": "Aberdeen FC vs. Livingston FC: O/U 1.5",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a336461613134336664643430656137356465326266656463666139336338393964363331653630333163623963353035643966303634633133353735653934322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323034373134342c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769214152,
        "question": "Will the highest temperature in London be 11°C or higher on January 23?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a356263326365396130353766323436643964353338383836303730366665663137323235343661616537343232333030366461393635616132336136383165312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323034353037352c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769210060,
        "question": "Will Trump's approval rating be between 41.0 and 41.4 on January 23, 2026?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a363138386263633766303632323237666639326264616133393963363265656165663734616635613863373737396536613134336239353836333230636338662c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323034343937312c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769203156,
        "question": "BPL: Chattogram Challengers vs Durbar Rajshahi (Game 1) - Toss Match Double Durbar Rajshahi Winner",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a366665643333653638393764306130343263656665343532623833373966383833633934623831396131383866303065616439626234636332353962663366382c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323033393631302c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769198812,
        "question": "No change in Fed interest rates after January 2026 meeting?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a656164303632343230373538646534343533363830643535323837323434666632306366313430396661613261366239303234306139316534336330633731342c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323033383539322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769196082,
        "question": "Will the US strike Iran next?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a633735366137623736353538613433376461316437613163616135313262636335393562306261643037633534653330643965353061316366346166363637312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323033383535322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769196068,
        "question": "Will the US strike Iraq next?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a366436643933613535343634633061343565623361643133386433623038613064623333363363663137383932326137653035663031323262313933646637322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323033383533392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769196050,
        "question": "Will the US strike Somalia next?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a366436643933613535343634633061343565623361643133386433623038613064623333363363663137383932326137653035663031323262313933646637322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323033373230302c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769194138,
        "question": "Will the US strike Somalia next?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a366665643333653638393764306130343263656665343532623833373966383833633934623831396131383866303065616439626234636332353962663366382c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323033373039312c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769193132,
        "question": "No change in Fed interest rates after January 2026 meeting?",
        "answer": "P4"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a343139323936623335323631623830656665666233396538353763666464313438333164356432613137653463643166316464363636623235653730353630322c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323032373837322c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769174774,
        "question": "Series: EDward Gaming Kill Handicap (-13.5) vs ThunderTalk Gaming (+13.5)",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a623362623232636664666538613765633564373765396361356161366666383963633232393234386535306261653265623461653633336362616437336435352c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323030393934392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769136214,
        "question": "Who will win: HOU vs PHI?",
        "answer": "P1"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a306464356234373439353639656465313832663066363536656534653965386638343737633264636463383165373335393733306463633037373363333633382c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38323030313637392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769122120,
        "question": "LoL: Deer Gaming vs La BOMBAS (BO1) - NLC Regular Season",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a633738636630656533323834356536366332336361643639653665653333373936313364343265626434643366326136626534343137393138333533626164382c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38313939393639392c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a656533616665333437643563373433313730343165323631386334393533346461663838376332342c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769117666,
        "question": "Will the highest temperature in Wellington be 22°C or higher on January 23?",
        "answer": "P2"
    },
    {
        "ancillaryData": "0x616e63696c6c61727944617461486173683a323864363739356564373037383838396533316336656438663331326461336337343634303137393439316439623733386266356238346362633562646236312c6368696c64426c6f636b4e756d6265723a38313939373832352c6368696c644f7261636c653a616336303335336135343837336334343631303132313638323961366139386364626263336633642c6368696c645265717565737465723a326330333637613964623233316464656264383861393462346636343631613665343763353862312c6368696c64436861696e49643a313337",
        "timestamp": 1769111800,
        "question": "Tesla launches unsupervised full self driving (FSD) by March 31?",
        "answer": "P4"
    }
]
